const STORE = [
  {},
  {
    question: 'Lynyrd Skynyrd had a massive hit with which song that was also the title of a film starring Reese Witherspoon, Josh Lucas and Patrick Dempsey?',
    answers: [
      'Free Bird',
      'Sweet Home Alabama',
      'Tuesday\'s Gone',
      'Simple Man'
    ],
    correct: 'Sweet Home Alabama'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who of the following was formerly a member of the British group Buffalo Springfield?',
    answers: [
      'David Crosby',
      'Stephen Stills',
      'Neil Young',
      'Graham Nash'
    ],
    correct: 'Stephen Stills'
  },
  {
    question: 'Perhaps the best known band of all time, The Beatles had many hits. Which of these isn\'t one of them?',
    answers: [
      'Day Tripper',
      'I Want to Hold Your Hand',
      'Can\'t Buy Me Love',
      'Band on the Run'
    ],
    correct: 'Band on the Run'
  },
  {
    question: 'What band features brothers Eddie and Alex on guitar and drums, respectively?',
    answers: [
      'Van Halen',
      'The Allman Brothers Band',
      'The Everly Brothers',
      'The Avett Brothers'
    ],
    correct: 'Van Halen'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is a well-known Cream song?',
    answers: [
      'Lick it Up',
      'Killer Queen',
      'One of These Days',
      'Sunshine of Your Love'
    ],
    correct: 'Sunshine of Your Love'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year did the Beatles perform their last live show (not including Apple rooftop show)?',
    answers: [
      '1974',
      '1966',
      '1962',
      '1971'
    ],
    correct: '1966'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who co-wrote The Eagles\' song "Take It Easy" with Glenn Frey?',
    answers: [
      'Jackson Browne',
      'Tom Petty',
      'Don Henley',
      'Joe Walsh'
    ],
    correct: 'Jackson Browne'
  },
  {
    question: '"Come out Virginia, don\'t let me wait, you Catholic girls start much too late..."',
    answers: [
      'Phil Collins',
      'Billy Joel',
      'Elvis Presley',
      'Eric Clapton'
    ],
    correct: 'Billy Joel'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which 1973 Pink Floyd hit has a lengthy introduction consisting of clocks chiming and alarms ringing?',
    answers: [
      'Money',
      'Another Brick in the Wall',
      'Time',
      'Comfortably Numb'
    ],
    correct: 'Time'
  },
  {
    question: 'Anyone familiar with the Grateful Dead knows that Jerry Garcia was the heart of the group. His vocals and lead guitar style are well-known. However, their rhythm guitarist shared lead vocal and songwriting duties with Garcia for most of the band\'s thirty year run. Who was this other guy?',
    answers: [
      'Phil Lesh',
      'Mikey Hart',
      'Bill Kreutzmann',
      'Bob Weir'
    ],
    correct: 'Bob Weir'
  },
]